const section_01 = [
  {
    questionID: "01.01",
    question:
      "Who is the overall responsible for working-life linkages at the UoA?",
    answers: [
      "UoA director",
      "Specially appointed teacher or other staff",
      "Other, please specify below",
      "I do not know",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1, 1.5, 0.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "01.02",
    question: "Please specify.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "01.01",
    dependingAnswer: ["Other, please specify below"],
    score: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "01.03",
    question:
      "Which of the following are involved in the planning of work-integrated learning at the UoA?",
    answers: [
      "UoA director",
      "Teachers",
      "Students",
      "Alumni",
      "External contacts",
      "Other, please specify below",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1.5, 0.5, 2, 1, 1, 0.6],
  },
  {
    questionID: "01.04",
    question: "Please specify.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "01.03",
    dependingAnswer: ["Other, please specify below"],
    score: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "01.05",
    question:
      "Is work-integrated learning at the UoA coordinated with other education programmes within or outside the university?",
    answers: ["Yes, regularly", "Yes, occasionally", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1.5, 1, 0.6],
  },
  {
    questionID: "01.06",
    question: "What does the coordination entail?",
    answers: [
      "Overall planning",
      "Resource sharing/pooling",
      "Specific activities",
      "Evaluations",
      "Other, please elaborate below",
    ],
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "01.05",
    dependingAnswer: ["Yes, occasionally"],
    scores: [1.5, 0.5, 1, 2, 0.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "01.07",
    question: "Please elaborate.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "01.06",
    dependingAnswer: ["Other, please elaborate below"],
    scores: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "01.08",
    question:
      "Is there an earmarked budget at the UoA for work-integrated integration?",
    answers: ["Yes, for staff time", "Yes, for direct costs", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1.5, 0.5, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "01.09",
    question:
      "Is there additional funding for work-integrated learning at any higher administrative level for which the UoA can apply?",
    answers: ["Yes, regularly", "Yes, occasionally", "No", "I do not know"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1.5, 1, 2],
  },
  {
    questionID: "01.10",
    question:
      "Is work-integrated learning a separate budget line in the UoA's financial records and reports?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No", "I do not know"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [0.5, 1],
  },
];

const section_02 = [
  {
    questionID: "02.01",
    question:
      "Has the UoA defined aims and objectives for work-integrated learning?",
    answers: ["Yes, several", "Yes, one", "No ", "Do not know"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1, 0.5, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.02",
    question: "To what extent are the aims and objectives met?",
    answers: [
      "Completely",
      "To a large extent",
      "To a small extent",
      "Not at all",
    ],
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "02.01",
    dependingAnswer: ["Yes, several", "Yes, one"],
    scores: [0.5, 1, 2, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.03",
    question:
      "Does the UoA have a strategy for achieving the aims and objectives?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No"],
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "02.01",
    dependingAnswer: ["Yes, several", "Yes, one"],
    scores: [2, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.04",
    question: "How often is the strategy revised?",
    answers: [
      "Every two years or more often",
      "Every three to five years",
      "Less than every five-year",
    ],
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "02.03",
    dependingAnswer: ["Yes"],
    scores: [2, 0.7, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.05",
    question:
      "When do the students get their first information about work-integrated learning in their education?",
    answers: [
      "In their first year",
      "In their second year",
      "In their third year or later",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [0.7, 1.5, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.06",
    question:
      "Is work-integrated learning evaluated at the UoA? (Either as part of a broader assessment or separately)",
    answers: ["Yes, once a year or more often", "Yes, occasionally", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [0, 0.7, 1.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.07",
    question: "Who are involved in the assessments?",
    answers: [
      "Students",
      "Teachers",
      "UoA director",
      "Director of Studies",
      "A UEC office",
      "External partners",
      "Other, please elaborate below",
    ],
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "02.06",
    dependingAnswer: ["Yes, once a year or more often", "Yes, occasionally"],
    scores: [2, 1, 0.5, 1, 2, 1.5, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.08",
    question: "What other role(s) are involved?",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "02.07",
    dependingAnswer: ["Other, please elaborate below"],
    scores: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.09",
    question: "Who uses the assessment results?",
    answers: [
      "Curriculum Committee",
      "Instructor team",
      "Director of Studies",
      "University Management",
      "Other, please elaborate below",
    ],
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "02.06",
    dependingAnswer: ["Yes, once a year or more often", "Yes, occasionally"],
    scores: [1, 1.2, 2, 1.5, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.10",
    question: "Please indicate what context(s) the results are used in.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "02.09",
    dependingAnswer: ["Other, please elaborate below"],
    scores: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.11",
    question:
      "How does the UoA ensure that the number of work-integrated learning activities is appropriate?",
    answers: [
      "Through advisory/regulatory bodies",
      "Through dialogue with teachers",
      "Through dialogue with external partners",
      "Through dialogue with students",
      "In evaluations",
      "In other ways, please elaborate below",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1.5, 0, 1, 1.2, 3],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.12",
    question: "Please elaborate.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "02.11",
    dependingAnswer: ["In other ways, please elaborate below"],
    scores: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.13",
    question:
      "How does the UoA ensure that the character of work-integrated learning activities is appropriate in terms of types, regularity, and variation?",
    answers: [
      "Through advisory/regulatory bodies",
      "Through dialogue with teachers",
      "Through dialogue with external partners",
      "In discussions with students",
      "Included in evaluations",
      "Other way, please elaborate below",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1.5, 0, 1, 1.2, 3],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.14",
    question: "Please elaborate.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "02.13",
    dependingAnswer: ["Other way"],
    scores: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.15",
    question:
      "Does the UoA follow up with alums to investigate what long-term results the work-integrated learning activities led to?",
    answers: ["Yes, annually", "Yes, biennially", "Yes, occasionally", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [0, 1, 1.2, 3],
  },
  {
    questionID: "02.16",
    question:
      "Does the UoA follow up with employers/external partners to investigate what long-term results the work-integrated learning activities lead to?",
    answers: ["Yes, annually", "Yes, biennially", "Yes, occasionally", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1.5, 3, 1],
  },
];

const section_03 = [
  {
    questionID: "03.01",
    question:
      "Who provides ideas for work-integrated learning activities (e.g., ideas about activities, content or invitees)?",
    answers: [
      "Students",
      "UoA director",
      "Teachers/Staff",
      "External contacts",
      "Others, please specify below",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1.5, 0, 3, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "03.02",
    question: "Please specify.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "03.01",
    dependingAnswer: ["Others, please specify below"],
    scores: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "03.03",
    question:
      "Are students encouraged to propose ideas for work-integrated learning activities?",
    answers: ["Yes, regularly", "Yes, occasionally", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1, 1.2, 3],
  },
  {
    questionID: "03.04",
    question:
      "Are teachers and staff encouraged to propose ideas for work-integrated learning activities?",
    answers: ["Yes, regularly", "Yes, occasionally", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1.5, 3],
  },
  {
    questionID: "03.05",
    question: "How do you strategically develop work-integrated learning?",
    answers: [
      "An appointed person",
      "In a standing group/team",
      "In dedicated projects",
      "In other ways, please elaborate below",
      "N/A",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [0, 1, 0.5, 3, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "03.06",
    question: "Please elaborate.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "03.05",
    dependingAnswer: ["In other ways, please elaborate below"],
    scores: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "03.07",
    question:
      "Are students generally encouraged to carry out extracurricular work-integrated learning activities?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "03.08",
    question:
      "Who ensures that the UoA's work-integrated learning activities are up to date with the latest developments in the industry?",
    answers: [
      "Students",
      "Teachers/Staff",
      "UoA director",
      "Others, please specify below",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1, 1.5, 0.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "03.09",
    question: "Please specify.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "03.08",
    dependingAnswer: ["Others, please specify below"],
    scores: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "03.10",
    question:
      "How does the UoA ensure the relevance of work-integrated learning activities?",
    answers: [
      "General news coverage",
      "Industry-specific news coverage (e.g., websites and industry magazines)",
      "External representation at the UoA",
      "Participation in professional fairs/conferences",
      "Staff actively participate in industry associations/networks",
      "Personal external contacts",
      "Alumni contacts",
      "Knowledge exchange with programmes at other universities",
      "Other ways, please elaborate below",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "03.11",
    question: "Please elaborate.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "03.10",
    dependingAnswer: ["Other ways, please elaborate below"],
    scores: [1],
  },
];

const section_04 = [
  {
    questionID: "04.01",
    question:
      "Is there a career centre at the university where the students can go for information and support?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "04.02",
    question: "Is there any interaction between the UoA and the career centre?",
    answers: ["Yes, often", "Yes, occasionally", "No"],
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "04.01",
    dependingAnswer: ["Yes"],
    scores: [1, 1.5, 0.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "04.03",
    question: "Do you invite alums to work-integrated learning activities?",
    answers: [
      "Yes, as speakers, workshop facilitators etc.",
      "Yes, as participants/audience",
      "No",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1, 1.5, 0.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "04.04",
    question:
      "Do you connect work-integrated learning activities with ongoing research? (e.g., workshops with researchers and professionals participating.)",
    answers: ["Yes, often", "Yes, occasionally", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1, 0.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "04.05",
    question: "Is work-integrated learning described in the UoA’s syllabus?",
    answers: ["Yes, thoroughly described", "Yes, but only briefly", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1, 1.5, 0.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "04.06",
    question:
      "Does the UoA’s syllabus specify learning outcomes for work-integrated learning activities?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "04.07",
    question: "Do the learning outcomes include any of the following?",
    answers: [
      "Deepening/broadening of knowledge related to the degree program",
      "Applying critical thinking",
      "Ethical perspectives/issues",
      "Building self-confidence",
      "Networking",
      "Experience with workplaces and professionalism",
      "Starting and running a business",
    ],
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "04.06",
    dependingAnswer: ["Yes"],
    scores: [2, 1, 0, 1.5, 0.5, 1, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "04.08",
    question: "To what extent are the learning outcomes met?",
    answers: [
      "Completely",
      "To a large extent",
      "To some extent",
      "Not at all",
    ],
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "04.06",
    dependingAnswer: ["Yes"],
    scores: [2, 1.5, 0.5, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "04.09",
    question:
      "How many of the UoA’s work-integrated learning activities connect directly to the topic of specific courses, i.e., not generic?",
    answers: ["A majority ", "A minority", "Not at all"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1.5, 0.5, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "04.10",
    question:
      "How many of the UoA’s work-integrated learning activities are compulsory?",
    answers: ["A majority ", "A minority", "None"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1.5, 0.5, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "04.11",
    question:
      "How often do joint work-integrated learning activities occur with students in other educational programmes?",
    answers: [
      "Several times a year",
      "A few times a year",
      "Occasionally",
      "Never",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1, 1.5, 0.5],
  },
];

const section_05 = [
  {
    questionID: "05.01",
    question:
      "Does each work-integrated learning activity have specific learning outcomes?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "05.02",
    question:
      "In what ways are students informed about the education’s work-integrated learning activities?",
    answers: [
      "Orally, e.g., in connection with lectures",
      "In a study guide or similar",
      "By email",
      "At a specific website",
      "Social Media",
      "Other, please elaborate below",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1, 1.5, 0.5, 1, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "05.03",
    question: "Please elaborate.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "05.02",
    dependingAnswer: ["Other, please elaborate below"],
    scores: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "05.04",
    question:
      "How often do you estimate that students generally receive information about their future careers?",
    answers: ["1-2 times per semester", "1-3 times per month", "Every week"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1, 1.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "05.05",
    question:
      "Are the individual work-integrated learning activities evaluated?",
    answers: ["Yes, always", "Yes, sometimes", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1, 0.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "05.06",
    question: "Who is involved in the evaluations?",
    answers: [
      "The person/persons who held the activity (e.g., a guest lecturer)",
      "The person/persons who organised the activity (e.g., a teacher)",
      "The students",
      "Other, please elaborate below",
    ],
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "05.05",
    dependingAnswer: ["Yes, always", "Yes, sometimes"],
    scores: [2, 1, 1.5, 0.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "05.07",
    question: "Please elaborate.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "05.06",
    dependingAnswer: ["Other, please elaborate below"],
    scores: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "05.08",
    question: "What do the evaluations assess?",
    answers: [
      "The information before the activity",
      "The  pedagogical quality of the activity",
      "The  knowledge contribution of the activity",
      "The  activity’s level of difficulty",
      "The  activity’s relevance",
      "The  coherence of the learning outcomes",
      "Other, please elaborate below",
    ],
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "05.05",
    dependingAnswer: ["Yes, always", "Yes, sometimes"],
    scores: [2, 1, 1.5, 0.5, 1, 1.5, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "05.09",
    question: "Please elaborate.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "05.08",
    dependingAnswer: ["Other, please elaborate below"],
    scores: [1],
  },
];

const section_06 = [
  {
    questionID: "06.01",
    question:
      "Is there a central office or function for work-integrated learning at the university?",
    answers: [
      "Yes, at the university/college level",
      "Yes, at the faculty/school level",
      "Yes, at a more local level than the above, e.g. department level",
      "No",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1, 1.5, 0.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "06.02",
    question: "Is the support you receive from the central office sufficient?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No"],
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "06.01",
    dependingAnswer: [
      "Yes, at the university/college level",
      "Yes, at the faculty/school level",
      "Yes, at a more local level than the above, e.g. department level",
    ],
    scores: [2, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "06.03",
    question:
      "Is work-integrated learning on the agenda in general department meetings?",
    answers: ["Yes, regularly", "Yes, occasionally", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "06.04",
    question:
      "Can you comfortably address questions about work-integrated learning in the relevant department meetings?",
    answers: [
      "Yes, without problems",
      "Yes, but only if it is a crucial question",
      "No, I avoid that",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1, 1, 1.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "06.05",
    question:
      "Would you say the UoA’s faculty and staff are generally interested in work-integrated learning?",
    answers: [
      "Yes, very interested",
      "Yes, somewhat interested",
      "No, not particularly interested",
      "No, not at all interested",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [0.5, 1, 1.5, 2],
  },
  {
    questionID: "06.06",
    question:
      "Does your closest manager support your efforts in work-integrated learning?",
    answers: ["Yes, to a large extent", "Yes, to some extent", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1.5, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "06.07",
    question:
      "Does the university have articulated objectives regarding work-integrated learning?",
    answers: [
      "Yes, at the university/college level",
      "Yes, at the faculty/school level",
      "Yes, at the department level",
      "No",
      "I do not know",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1, 2, 3, 4, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "06.08",
    question:
      "Are there any earmarked funds allocated for work-integrated learning activities?",
    answers: [
      "Yes, at the university/college level",
      "Yes, at the faculty/school level",
      "Yes, at the department level",
      "No",
      "I do not know",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [4, 3, 2, 1, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "06.09",
    question:
      "Are there any instructions, training, or guidance available for how to work with work-integrated learning?",
    answers: [
      "Yes, at the university/college level",
      "Yes, at the faculty/school level",
      "Yes, at the department level or more locally",
      "No",
      "I do not know",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1, 1.5, 0.5, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "06.10",
    question:
      "Is there a general follow-up mechanism regarding work-integrated learning?",
    answers: [
      "Yes, at the university/college level",
      "Yes, at the faculty/school level",
      "Yes, at the department level or more locally",
      "No",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1, 2, 1.5, 0.5],
  },
];

const section_07 = [
  {
    questionID: "07.01",
    question:
      "At how many external events, such as conferences and trade fairs, is the UoA represented in a year?",
    answers: ["0", "1-2", "3-4", ">4"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1, 1, 1.5, 0.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "07.02",
    question:
      "Is any UoA staff engaged in formal industry networks or interest organisations?",
    answers: ["Yes, in several", "Yes, in a few", "No", "I do not know"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1.5, 1, 0.5],
  },
  {
    questionID: "07.03",
    question:
      "Does anyone in the UoA staff hold a formal role in any external bodies? (e.g. board position, project manager)?",
    answers: ["Yes, in several", "Yes, in a few", "No"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1, 1.5, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "07.04",
    question:
      "Have you assigned anyone to monitor the latest developments in the relevant industries?",
    answers: [
      "Yes, students",
      "Yes, teachers/staff",
      "Yes, the UoA director",
      "Yes, someone else,Please specify below",
      "No",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1.5, 1, 0.5, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "07.05",
    question: "Please specify.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "07.04",
    dependingAnswer: ["Yes, someone else,Please specify below"],
    scores: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "07.06",
    question: "In what ways does the monitoring take place?",
    answers: [
      "General news coverage",
      "Industry-specific news coverage (e.g. groups on the internet or industry magazines)",
      "Participation in fairs/conferences",
      "Staff actively participate in industry associations/networks",
      "Personal industry contacts",
      "Alumni contacts",
      "Talking to corresponding program staff at other universities",
      "In other ways, please elaborate below",
    ],
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "07.04",
    dependingAnswer: [
      "Yes, students",
      "Yes, teachers/staff",
      "Yes, the UoA director",
      "Yes, someone else,Please specify below",
    ],
    scores: [2, 1.5, 1, 0.5, 1.5, 1, 0.5, 0],
  },
  {
    questionID: "07.07",
    question: "Please elaborate.",
    dependOn: true,
    dependingQuestion: "07.06",
    dependingAnswer: ["In other ways, please elaborate below"],
    scores: [1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "07.08",
    question:
      "Is work-integrated learning at the UoA described in marketing material?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No", "I do not know"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [0.5, 1.5, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "07.09",
    question:
      "Is work-integrated learning at the UoA described on the public website?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No", "I do not know"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1.5, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "07.10",
    question: "Is the UoA active/visible on social media?",
    answers: [
      "Very active (often posts news and pictures, starts, and engages in discussions, answers questions etc.)",
      "Slightly active (same as above but to a lesser extent)",
      "Passive presence (only answers questions)",
      "Not present on social media",
    ],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [1, 0.5, 1.5, 1],
  },
  {
    questionID: "07.11",
    question:
      "How many formal news or press releases does the UoA publish in a semester?",
    answers: ["0-1", "1-2", "2-5", ">5"],
    dependOn: false,
    dependingQuestion: null,
    dependingAnswer: null,
    scores: [2, 1.5, 1, 0.5],
  },
];

export {
  section_01,
  section_02,
  section_03,
  section_04,
  section_05,
  section_06,
  section_07,
};
